let questions = [
  {
    question: "What is the name of the snail Gary falls in love with?",
    answers: ["Penelope", "Jessica", "Cynthia", "Mary"],
    correctAnswer: "Mary",
    name: "q1"
  },
  {
    question: "What does Mermaid Main wear on his feet?",
    answers: [
      "Blue fuzzy slippers",
      "Fuzzy pink slippers",
      "Soccer cleats",
      "Bananas"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Fuzzy pink slippers",
    name: "q2"
  },

  {
    question:
      "When Spongebob and Patrick adopt a baby scallop,What did they name it?",
    answers: [" Junior", "7", "Lil Fry", "Melvin"],
    correctAnswer: "Junior",
    name: "q3"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Mr.Krabs' pet worm?",
    answers: ["Krabby Worm", "Turd", "Whichsideisthehead WIlly", "Mr.Doodles"],
    correctAnswer: "Mr.Doodles",
    name: "q4"
  },
  {
    question: "Who are Spongebob's parents?",
    answers: [
      "Harold & Margaret Squarepants",
      "Ren & Stimpy Squarepants",
      "Charles & Judy Squarepants",
      "Terry & Terri Squrepants"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Harold & Margaret Squarepants",
    name: "q5"
  },
  {
    question: "Who exercises on a hamster wheel?",
    answers: ["Mrs.Puff", "Patrick", " Squidward", "Sandy"],
    correctAnswer: "Sandy",
    name: "q6"
  },
  {
    question: "When did Spongebob get his boating license?",
    answers: [
      "When he was born",
      "Never",
      "After Mrs.Puff gave up",
      "On his 5th try"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "When he was born",
    name: "q7"
  },
  {
    question: "WHo signs a spatula for Spongebob?",
    answers: [
      "Larry the Lobster",
      "Taylor Swift",
      "Barnacle Boy",
      "Kenny the Cat"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Kenny the Cat",
    name: "q8"
  },
  {
    question: "What does Gary do on Opposite Day?",
    answers: [
      "Wash Squidward'feet",
      "Eat olive nachos",
      "Take off his shell",
      "Bark"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Bark",
    name: "q9"
  },
  {
    question: "What color are Patrick's shorts?",
    answers: [
      "Green and Purple",
      "Pink and Blue",
      "Patrick doesn't wear pants",
      "Yellow and Pink"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Green and Purple",
    name: "q10"
  }
];
